we've been asked
to edit the given code so that it does
print the method parameter words to the
screen
the reason that our method doesn't
currently print anything to the screen
is because we return from the method
prior to executing the code on line 4
where we pass words to the method put us
so to make sure that we execute the code
on that line
we can remove the reserved word return
from line three
after doing so when our method is
invoked both lines two
and three will be executed and words
will be output to the
screen
we can run our code to see this
and there's the string as expected
the second part of this problem asks us
what are method returns
previously when we had a return on line
our method returned nil and we can see
that when we leave the return on line 3
and use p to print the return value
of invoking our screen method
now when we run our code we see that the
return value of the method is nil
if we were to place some additional code
on line 3
ruby would return the evaluated result
of that expression
for example if we want to return words
explicitly
we can do so on line three now when we
run our code
and use p to output the return value
we see that the string referenced by
words is returned
so the problem asks us now that we have
removed the explicit return from our
method
what will the return value of this
method be
without an explicit return in our method
the return value will be the evaluated
result
of the last line executed in this case
the last line executed in our method
will be line
three on line three we invoked the put s
method
which always returns nil so one last
time we will
invoke our screen method and output its
return value with p
we expect to see the words string output
and then nil when we output the return
value of this method
and that's what we see
you